{
    "subject": "Marco_Ferreri",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Don't_Touch_the_White_Woman!",
    "human_readable": "Marco Ferreri created the film Don't Touch the White Woman!",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8216339945793152,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'Don't Touch the White Woman!'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7764732241630554,
            "question": "What is the title of the film created by Marco Ferreri?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7225464582443237,
            "question": "What year was the film 'Don't Touch the White Woman!' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6979244351387024,
            "question": "Has the film 'Don't Touch the White Woman!' received critical acclaim?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6391545534133911,
            "question": "Where was 'Don't Touch the White Woman!' filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6171057224273682,
            "question": "What genre might the film 'Don't Touch the White Woman!' belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5692554712295532,
            "question": "Is Marco Ferreri known for directing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5421233177185059,
            "question": "What is the main plot of 'Don't Touch the White Woman!'"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47164371609687805,
            "question": "Are there any other films directed by Marco Ferreri?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4514896869659424,
            "question": "What themes might be explored in 'Don't Touch the White Woman!'"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Marco Ferreri created the film Don't Touch the White Woman!",
            "html": "yago_8380_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other films directed by Marco Ferreri?",
            "html": "yago_8380_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the main plot of 'Don't Touch the White Woman!'",
            "html": "yago_8380_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Marco Ferreri known for directing films?",
            "html": "yago_8380_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8380_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8380_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8380_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8380_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8380_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8380_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8380_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8380_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8380_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8380_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of whether the triple supports the statement:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that while there are several documents mentioning the film \"Don't Touch the White Woman!\" and Marco Ferreri as its director, there is no direct statement or evidence in the provided context information suggesting that Marco Ferreri created the film. The documents provide more of a descriptive nature, with some containing factual information about the film, but none explicitly state that Ferreri created it."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Marco Ferreri and his film \"Don\u2019t Touch the White Woman!\" which supports the statement that Marco Ferreri created this film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}